Rick Whitesell Record Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. "Goldmine" and Other Publications, 6; 7.5 linear feet Boxes:1 - 5 Folders: 6.1 - 6.96
  - Issue No. 89 Goldmine, October 1983; 1 Copy (Folder 58, Box 4)
  - Issue No. 90 Goldmine, November 1983; 1 Copy (Folder 59, Box 4)
  - Issue No. 91 Goldmine, December 1983; 1 Copy (Folder 60, Box 4)
  - Issue No. 92 Goldmine, January 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 61, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 93 Goldmine, February 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 62, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 94 Goldmine, March 2, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 63, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 95 Goldmine, March 16, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 64, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 96 Goldmine, March 30, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 65, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 97 Goldmine, April 13, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 66, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 98 Goldmine, April 27 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 67, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 99 Goldmine, May 11, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 68, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 100 Goldmine, May 25, 1984; 5 Copies (Folder 69, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 101 Goldmine, June 8, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 70, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 102 Goldmine, June 22, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 71, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 103 Goldmine, July 6, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 72, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 104 Goldmine, July 20, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 73, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 105 Goldmine, August 3,1984; 1 Copy (Folder 74, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 106 Goldmine, August 17, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 75, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 107 Goldmine, September 14 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 76, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 108 Goldmine, September 14, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 77, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 109 Goldmine, September 28, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 78, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 110 Goldmine, October 12, 1984; 1 Copy (Folder 79, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 165 Goldmine, November 21, 1986; 1 Copy (Folder 80, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 175 Goldmine, April 10, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 81, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 177 Goldmine, May 8, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 82, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 178 Goldmine, May 22, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 83, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 179 Goldmine, June 5, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 84, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 180 Goldmine, June 19, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 85, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 181 Goldmine, July 3, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 86, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 182 Goldmine, July 17, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 87, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 18? Goldmine, September 11, 1987; 1 Copy (no cover) (Folder 88, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 187 Goldmine, September 25, 1987; 1 Copy (Folder 89, Box 5)
  - Issue No. 204 Good Times: The Music &Entertainment Paper, August 28,1979; - (Folder 90, Box 6)
  - Issue No. 1 Classic Wax, October 1980; - (Folder 91, Box 7)
  - Issue No. 2 (2 Copies) Classic Wax, January 1981; 2 (Folder 92, Box 7)
  - Issue No. 4 Classic Wax, August 1981; - (Folder 93, Box 7)
  - Issue No. 1 Record Auction Monthly, July 1984; - (Folder 94, Box 8)
  - -The Rolling Stone Illustrated History Of Rock&Roll-, - (Folder 95, Box 9)
  - -Original Record Collector's Price Guide - 1st Edition-, - (Folder 96, Box 9)
- 7. Video Tapes, 7; 1.5 linear feet Box: 1 Folders: 7.1 - 7.5
  Alphabetical by Title
  - It Came From Hollywood Part One (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - It Came From Hollywood Part Two (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - When The Music's Over (59:00) 5/24/84 (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - When The Music's Over (12:00) Rough Cut, James Brown and Barry Gibb Interviews (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - Chuck Berry Interview, 12/17/82 (Folder 5, Box 1)
- 8. Books, 8; 1.5 linear feet Box: 1 Folders: 8.1 - 8.6
  Alphabetical by Author
  - From Satchmo to Miles, Feather, Leonard (Folder 1)
  - Youth Leisure and the Policics of Rock 'n' Roll, Frith, Simon; Sound Effects (Folder 2)
  - John Hammond On Record, Hammond, John (Folder 3)
  - Shout: The Beatles In Their Generation, Norman, Philip (Folder 4)
  - All American Music: Composition In The Late Twentieth Century, Rockwell, John (Folder 5)
  - Outlaw Blues, Williams, Paul (Folder 6)
- 9. Miscellaneous, 9; 3 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 3 No numbered folders
  Groupings
  - Other Materials (Box Box: 1)
  - List of Records in Collection (Box Box: 2)
  - Misc. Papers (Box Box: 3)